justskins.com 2005-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Xeonext

Xeonext is committed to user privacy in our products and services. This policy outlines our personal information handling practices. If you give us personal information, we will treat it according to this policy. Xeonext encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all Web sites you visit. 

**Security Measures**  
We protect the personal information you share with us. For example, if you make an online purchase with us, we encrypt your credit card number. Access to your personal information is limited to people who need it to do their job.  
Authorized third-party agents may also need access to some of your personal information. For example, if we need to ship something to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. We only provide third-party agents with the minimum amount of information needed to complete the requested service or transaction. We do not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you have granted us permission to do so.  
We may collect and possibly share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of 's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Data Retention**  
Xeonext will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected.

**Discussion Forums**  
Xeonext forums are public. Please consider this before posting.

**Policy Updates**  
All updates to this policy will be posted here.   
Need Help with an Update, Access, or Unsubscribe Request?  
Contact at: [info@xeonext.com](mailto:info@xeonext.com) to aid in processing your request, please include the following details: Contact information (your name, address, e-mail address, etc.) Name of the program where you want the update applied Details of the request (e.g. change of e-mail address, unsubscribe from a newsletter, review of personal information, etc.) Note: This policy also covers the personal information you provide to Customer Support.
